<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>
  <!-- Salutations -->
  <category>
    <pattern>*</pattern>
    <template>
        I'm sorry I don't understand that answer.
        <split/>
        <delay>2</delay>
        You can type 'Hello' to begin a dialog or modify your previous 
        input.
    </template>
  </category>
  <category>
    <pattern><set>greetings</set></pattern>
    <template>
        Hello! My name is SCAB. The Student Career Advisor Bot.
        <delay>3</delay>
        <split/>
        I match current students with prospective job opportunities.
        <delay>4</delay>
        <split/>
        Would you like help determining a career path?
    </template>
  </category>
  <!-- End Salutations -->
  
  <!-- Yes No Answers -->
  <category>
    <pattern>YES</pattern>
    <template>
        Fantastic! Please tell me what area interests you.
        <delay>3</delay>
        <split/>
        Keep in mind that your choice probably needs to align 
        with your degree path.
        <delay>3</delay>
        <ul>
            <li>Programming</li>
            <li>Administration</li>
            <li>Security</li>
        </ul>
    </template>
  </category>
  <category>
      <pattern>INTERESTS</pattern>
      <template>
        Please tell me what area interests you.
        <delay>3</delay>
        <ul>
            <li>Programming</li>
            <li>Administration</li>
            <li>Security</li>
        </ul>
      </template>
  </category>
  <category>
        <pattern>NO</pattern>
        <template>
            That's ok.
            <split/>
            <delay>2</delay>
            Just initiate a conversation with me by typing 'Hello' 
            if you change your mind.
        </template>
  </category>
  <!-- End Yes No Answers -->
  
  <!-- Main Categories -->
  <category>
      <pattern>PROGRAMMING</pattern>
      <template>
          What kind of programming do you think you would enjoy doing?
          <delay>3</delay>
          <ul>
              <li>Mobile</li>
              <li>Website</li>
              <li>Desktop</li>
          </ul>
      </template>
  </category>
  <category>
      <pattern>ADMINISTRATION</pattern>
      <template>
          What kind of Administration are you interested in?
          <delay>3</delay>
          <ul>
              <li>System Admin</li>
              <li>Database Admin</li>
              <li>Network Admin</li>
          </ul>
      </template>
  </category>
  <category>
      <pattern>SECURITY</pattern>
      <template>
          What kind of Security are you interested in?
          <delay>3</delay>
          <ul>
              <li>Cyber Security</li>
              <li>Network Security</li>
          </ul>
      </template>
  </category>
  <!-- End Main Categories -->
  
  <!-- Programming Replies -->
  <category>
      <pattern>MOBILE</pattern>
      <template>
          You should look into the role of Mobile Applications Developer.
          <delay>3</delay>
          <split/>
          Take a look at the responsibilities of a Mobile Applications Developer
          to make sure this sounds like it would interest you!
          <split/>
          <delay>3</delay>
          Mobile Application Developers develop applications intended 
          to be used on mobile devices such as Phones, Tablets, and 
          other handheld devices.
      </template>
  </category>
  <category>
      <pattern>WEBSITE</pattern>
      <template>
          Web Development may be suitable in your case.
          <split/>
          <delay>3</delay>
          Take a look at the responsibilities of a Web Developer
          to make sure this sounds like it would interest you!
          <delay>3</delay>
          <split/>
          A Web Developer is responsible for designing, implementing, and
          potentially maintain a customers website. A web developer takes into 
          account User Experience and Function, and does require a bit of graphic
          design inclination.
      </template>
  </category>
  <category>
      <pattern>DESKTOP</pattern>
      <template>
          Developing Desktop Applications may be right down your alley!
          <split/>
          <delay>3</delay>
          Take a look at the responsibilities of a Desktop Applications Developer
          to make sure this sounds like it would interest you!
          <delay>3</delay>
          <split/>
          A Desktop Application Developer is responsible for interpreting
          software requirements into a working application. Most Desktop
          Application Developers specialize into one type of software category,
          such as, accounting software, document processing, and potentially
          graphics software.
      </template>
  </category>
  <!-- End Programming Replies -->
  
  <!-- Administration Replies -->
    <category>
        <pattern><set>systemadmins</set></pattern>
        <template>
            System Administrators maintain software and hardware by 
            installing, updating, and monitoring Operating Systems, 
            applications, security tools, and other systems to maintain stability.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern><set>databaseadmins</set></pattern>
        <template>
            Database Administrators install and maintain databases by
            developing optimization processes, maintaining permissions, and
            creating update and management standards for all managed databases.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>NETWORK ADMIN</pattern>
        <template>
            Network Administrators are typically in charge of maintaining
            computer networks and solving issues with them. Some areas of
            responsibility include, installation of computer networks,
            identifying network issues, and solving network issues.
        </template>
    </category>
  <!-- End Administration Replies -->
  
  <!-- Security Replies -->
  <category>
      <pattern>CYBER SECURITY</pattern>
      <template>
          Cyber Security Analysts are in charge of protecting internet 
          connected systems and networks from outside attacks.
      </template>
  </category>
  <category>
      <pattern>NETWORK SECURITY</pattern>
      <template>
          Network security Analysts are generally in charge of
          protecting files and directories in a network of computers 
          against misuse, hacking, and unauthorized access to the network.
      </template>
  </category>
  <!-- End Security Replies -->
</aiml>
